<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Month1</string>

    <string name="app_title">Month 1 Recall &amp; Retrieval</string>
    <string name="theory_route">Theory</string>
    <string name="tell_and_show_route">Tell &amp; Show</string>
    <string name="hands_on_route">Hands-On</string>
    <string name="real_life_route">Real-Life</string>
    <string name="events">Events</string>

    <string name="back_button">Back Button</string>

    <string name="big_picture">The Big Picture</string>
    <string name="key_takeaways">Key Takeaways</string>
    <string name="apply">How I Will Apply Them</string>
    <string name="go_to_sessions">Go to sessions</string>

    <!-- Big Picture -->
    <string name="big_picture_body">
        From my time at KamiLimu so far, the overall lesson I have learnt is the importance
        of a growth mindset. Having this will enable me to keep improving myself and yearning to
        learn more every day, while also being humble enough to be cognizant of my inadequacies.
        This also helps me acknowledge the need for a safe space to accommodate me as well as the
        role I play in creating one for those around me.
    </string>

    <!-- Sessions -->
    <!-- Community Engagement Pillar -->
    <string name="community_engagement_pillar">Community Engagement</string>
    <string name="community_engagement_about">
        Fostering immersion in and giving back to the local and global tech and social communities.
    </string>

    <string name="launch">Launch</string>
    <string name="launch_takeaways">
        Public speaking - Make a special moment for your audience when telling a story. At the
        end, tell them how it made you feel, what it makes you think and what it made you do.
        “Never make a point without a story and never make a story without a point.
        KamiLimu’s journey - Dr Chao’s story of the journey she has been through over the
        seven previous cohorts up until now showed me that resilience gives birth to good things.
        I also noted that everything, whether good or bad, teaches you lessons and unfolds in
        your favour.
    </string>
    <string name="launch_apply">
        Even in the face of adversity, always keep trying and moving forward. Giving up may
        rob my future self of amazing opportunities.
        Public speaking skills may open new doors
        for me in the professional world as well as improve my ability to communicate.
    </string>

    <string name="meet_an_alumni">Meet An Alumni</string>
    <string name="meet_an_alumni_takeaways">
        Juggling between KamiLimu and school during my time as a mentee is all down to being very
        organised and intentional with how I manage my time.
        To get the most from my time as a mentee at KamiLimu, I will have to very actively
        participate in the activities/meetings. Putting my best foot forward is also crucial to
        this.
    </string>
    <string name="meet_an_alumni_apply">
        Making the most of the opportunities given to me will help me grow as an individual.
        Contribute to making the environment I work in with others a safe space. This will help
        bring out the best in everyone.
    </string>


    <!-- Personal Development Pillar -->
    <string name="personal_development_pillar">Personal Development</string>
    <string name="personal_development_about">
        Nurturing human skills that contribute towards holistic growth.
    </string>

    <string name="how_to_learn">How To Learn</string>
    <string name="how_to_learn_takeaways">
        Scientific approach - Understanding the science behind how the brain works can
        help me formulate new studying habits that will enable me to retain even more after reading.
        Diffuse mode and Focus mode are the two states whose activities I need to alternate between,
        to maximise the effectiveness of my study sessions and retention. Taking breaks in between
        periods of deep focus is key to this.
    </string>
    <string name="how_to_learn_apply">
        Structure the activities during my study sessions following the principles of diffuse
        and focus modes.Make use of active recall techniques such as taking notes, reflecting on
        what I have learnt and ensuring mastery of what I have learnt or what I am practising for.
    </string>
    

    <!-- Professional Development Pillar -->
    <string name="professional_development_pillar">Professional Development</string>
    <string name="professional_development_about">
        Building excellence in professional settings.
    </string>
    
    <string name="resume_writing">Resume Writing</string>
    <string name="resume_writing_takeaways">
        Resume structure - A resume should be very brief (1 page). Your resume\'s different
        sections and contents should be determined by the job you are applying for.
        Quantify and qualify - When describing your roles in the capacity you held in a certain
        professional role, always use numbers to quantify your achievements and contributions.
        Verify that what you include is truthful.
    </string>
    <string name="resume_writing_apply">
        Always doing my research of a company in which I am applying for a job. This will help me
        tailor my resume to the particular role.
        Keeping my resume very brief and using numbers and qualifying statements to describe
        roles in my experience section.
    </string>

    <string name="ict_cybersecurity">ICT - Cyber security</string>
    <string name="ict_cyber_takeaways">
        Cybersecurity can be divided into two main factions; red-team and blue-team. As a
        cybersecurity expert, you have to be innovative and think out of the box to be successful.
        Every career path, more so in tech, demands life-long learning. Things are always changing
        and you need to be flexible and ready to adapt to changes in the industry. Even with that
        said, mastering your fundamentals is the first step to this.
    </string>
    <string name="ict_cyber_apply">
        Keep a growth mentality in everything I do. This will help me bring out the best version
        of myself by continuously learning and improving my technical skills.
        Being a team player. This will enable me to work in harmony with my colleagues to
        achieve greater things as well as learn new things from them.
    </string>
    

    <!-- Innovation Pillar -->
    <string name="innovation_pillar">Innovation</string>
    <string name="innovation_about">
        Growing expertise in using human centered design to build solutions that address
        socioeconomic issues.
    </string>
    
    <string name="intro_to_innovation">Intro To Innovation</string>
    <string name="intro_to_innovation_takeaways">
        Different factors that make up a good innovation and how to measure the impact of
        your innovation.
        The importance of taking time to understand the context of the environment in which your
        product is being deployed, so that it suits the end user.
    </string>
    <string name="intro_to_innovation_apply">
        When developing a product, thinking of the value it will give your customer should be the
        main aspect guiding the process. Always put my customer first in my design process.
        Taking time to understand the environment and context of where my product will be
        used. Understand who my end-user is as well as differentiate between my customer and
        end-user when designing a product.
    </string>

    <string name="innovations_in_real_life">Innovations In Real Life</string>
    <string name="innovations_in_real_life_takeaways">
        What ClassifyMe is and the problem they aimed to solve. When coming up with their
        innovation, they focused on developing a product that addresses the end user\'s needs. I
        also learned about challenges when working as a team.
        Identifying opportunities by talking to people and empathising with them to
        discover their grievances and pain points caused by lack of or inadequacies of
        existing solutions.
    </string>
    <string name="innovations_in_real_life_apply">
        When developing a product, the end-user should be at the centre of the design
        process for my innovation.
        Doing my research on existing solutions in the market and identifying any possible
        loopholes that may give birth to my innovation.
        Getting someone with similar goals when selecting my startup partner.
    </string>

</resources>